https://lvcosmeticsurgery.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy – Julio Garcia MD Cosmetic & Plastic Surgery Clinic Las Vegas
Skip to contentJulio Garcia MD Cosmetic & Plastic Surgery Clinic Las Vegas
Youtube
HomeAboutDr. Julio GarciaMeet Our TeamOur OfficeIn The NewsKLAV Radio ShowTestimonialsYour ConsultationPatient InformationCommunity InvolvementFrequently Asked QuestionsServicesBreast SurgeryBreast AugmentationTypes of Breast ImplantsBreast LiftBodyLiposuctionTummy TuckUltrasound LipoplastyMommy MakeoverFaceFaceliftBrowliftNose SurgeryEar SurgeryEyelid SurgeryFacial ImplantsFor MenGynecomastiaNon-Surgical ProceduresInjectablesBOTOX® CosmeticDysportFacial FillersSculptra AestheticLaser ResurfacingLaser ToningTattoo RemovalCell TherapyBefore & After GallerySpecialsFinancingBlogContact UsLas Vegas LocationPRIVACY POLICYThis notice discloses the privacy practices for www.lvcosmeticsurgery.com. It applies only to information collected by this web site.What Information We GatherWe collect only information that you voluntarily give us via email or in other direct contact. Specifically, that would be:Your nameYour email addressYour telephone number(s)Your mailing addressPersonal health information (if you so choose)We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We will not, under any circumstances, sell or rent it to anyone, or share it with anyone outside our organization or website host and/or manager.How We Will Use Your InformationWe will use it only to respond to you about the reason you contacted us. Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.SecurityOnlineWe do not ask you to supply any credit card data or social security number via our website, and any personal health information you do supply is voluntary. You do not need to give details.OfflineWe protect your sensitive information offline. No-one is given access to it except employees who need it to contact you or set up your file.What You Can DoYou can opt out of any future contacts from us at any time by replying to a received email, asking us to discontinue them. We will then remove your email address from our list.By using the contact form or by calling 7028700058, you can:Learn what data we have about you, if anyChange or correct any data we have about youHave us delete any data we have about youExpress any concern you have about our use of your dataBe aware when you use any link we provide to leave our site. Read the privacy statements of any other site that collects personally identifiable information. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those other sites.If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, please contact us immediately via telephone at 7028700058 or via email.Contact Us Today
Your Name
Your Phone
Your email
Your message
By submitting you're accepting our terms and conditions.OUR SERVICESBreastFaceBodyFor MenNon-Surgical
Previous
Next
Toll Free: 1-888-FACES89
(702) 870-0058
5735 S. Fort Apache Rd.
Suite B
Las Vegas, NV 89148 Copyright © 2020 | Julio Garcia MD | LVCosmetic Surgery Las Vegas | Powered by OpesMagnaBreast Surgery HendersonLiposuction HendersonMommy Makeover HendersonTummy Tuck HendersonTerms and ConditionsPrivacy Policy
